http://www.lodinews.com/site/company_policies.html

Regional
U.S.
Lodi, CA
(95240)
Today
A few passing clouds. Low 34F. Winds S at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
A few passing clouds. Low 34F. Winds S at 5 to 10 mph.
Rack Locations
Privacy PolicyThe Lodi News considers your privacy important. We are committed to protecting the privacy of all those who provide us with their contact information while using our information, products, events, or services. This policy describes the ways that personally identifiable and anonymous information about our publication subscribers, online media product users, and event registrants is collected, how that information might be shared, and how someone can request changes to the way their personal information is used or shared.This Privacy Policy applies to websites operated by or on behalf of The Lodi News its subsidiaries, affiliates, divisions and related companies. This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected by The Lodi News.  Be aware that our websites may contain links to other websites that are maintained by third parties who are not required to comply with this Privacy Policy and for which The Lodi News has no responsibility. Please review the privacy policies on any external websites to determine their information handling practices.Personally identifiable information is information that can identify you, such as your full name, email address, postal address, and telephone number.We collect personally identifiable information that you choose to provide to us when you subscribe to our newspapers, sign up for email newsletters, enter a contest; participate in surveys, register for a web site, webcast; or otherwise communicate with us. When you provide this information to us, you are no longer anonymous.We also may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us.If you purchase products or services on our website or through one of our printed forms, you may choose to provide us with your credit card information.The Lodi News is not responsible for the information you volunteer about yourself in discussions in our forums or in publicly accessible interactions, or the information that you choose to make public in your member profile. To view or change your member profile, please return to the site where you registered.ANONYMOUS INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe use cookies and other Internet technologies to enrich your online experience by managing our website and email programs. Our cookies do not contain any information, in itself, that is personally identifiable.If your browser is set to allow cookies, we may store small amounts of information on your computer about what parts of our websites you have visited and what features you like best. We may then tailor the content you see to match your interests. We also may use cookies to identify members so that they don't have to re-enter their usernames and passwords. Cookies may also be used to limit the number of advertisements you see while on our site. By allowing us to understand how you use our site over time, cookies can help us provide you with a better, more relevant online experience. The cookies we store on your computer are not accessible on any other companies' websites. Some ads on our site are provided by outside companies. If these ads contain cookies, they can be accessed only by those advertisers; we do not have access to them.Most browsers allow you to modify your security to accept or reject cookies. You need not have cookies turned on to visit our sites, but without them, your access to some areas may be limited and custom navigation may not be available to you.Like many websites, The Lodi News may use pixel tags. Pixel tags help us improve our understanding of our web traffic and visitor behavior, as well as gauge the response to our promotional efforts. This information is non-personally identifiable and is used for an aggregate picture of how visitors use our site.We may use industry-standard, third party advertising service companies to serve advertisements when you visit our sites or open our emails. These companies may use cookies, pixel tags, and other methods to collect information (typically not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our website and other web sites to provide you with relevant advertisements about products, services, and events tailored to your interests. You may opt out of receiving targeted advertising from several advertising networks by visiting a website operated by the National Advertising Initiative.  Go to http://optout.networkadvertising.org to opt out of several third-party advertiser networks by using a tool created by the Network Advertising InitiativeWe may use your contact information for any of the following reasons:To provide you with information about products or services you've ordered, or show interest in;We may also use your contact information to ask for your input to help in our research about our services, events, or products or to provide you with additional information about this site and about other The Lodi News products, services, or events that we think might be of interest to you.All promotional and research email messages you receive from us will include an option to opt out of future email communications from that particular Lodi News business.We may also send you e-newsletters with targeted, relevant content. Each e-newsletter will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of that particular e-newsletter.In some cases, we may send you relevant, carefully-screened offers from reputable third-party businesses or organizations. Many of our customers appreciate receiving these offers because they relate to their business or occupation. However, you will always be able to opt out of receiving future third party offers.We may provide contact lists to third party companies that we have employed to provide us with specialized services, including customer service, subscription fulfillment, research, statistical analysis, list cleansing, postal mailings, email deployment, telemarketing, and other information services. In compliance with privacy laws, we also provide our opt-out lists to those third-party companies so that they can be suppressed from the communications those companies send on The Lodi News’ behalf. We only deal with third party companies whom we believe share our commitment to privacy and who will keep your information secure.If you provide information on a co-branded site or while using a co-branded service, you grant us permission to share the information you have provided with that service or site partner. Their use of your information is subject to their privacy policies.Certain information, such as your password and credit card information, is never disclosed in any form whatsoever to any outside party.In the case of a change of ownership or a merger involving The Lodi News or any business that is part of The Lodi News, your contact information associated with that business would be one of those transferred assets.We use reasonable precautions, including appropriate technical, administrative, and physical procedures, to protect personal information from loss, misuse, or alteration.When we contract with other companies to provide us with services, we only share personal information with those that we believe share our commitment to privacy and information security. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of these parties.Due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.By using any of our websites, you consent to our use of your contact information as it is outlined in this privacy statement.The Lodi News reserves the right to access and disclose personally identifiable information to comply with applicable laws, lawful government requests and court orders, or to investigate alleged fraud or violations of the Terms of Use of The Lodi News website.If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post the changes on this page. Users are encouraged to review this page for any changes. Your continued use of this site constitutes your acceptance of this entire privacy statement.If you wish to contact The Lodi News about its privacy policy, please send your specific questions to: melissah@lodinews.com. Copyright NoticeThank you for using Lodinews.com.Material on this Web site is copyrighted by the Lodi News-Sentinel, unless otherwise indicated. It may be downloaded and reproduced by private individuals and political candidates according to the following restrictions:Lodinews.com is credited on any Web or printed page on which the material is reproduced.The reproduction is done verbatim or is shortened in a manner that is not misleading or unfaithful to the entirety of the original article.Applicable fees (if any) have been paid.Permission to reproduce must be requested from Lodinews.com if the reuse is for commercial purposes such as reselling the material, selling advertising on a site or print publication in which the material is reproduced or using material to promote the sale of a product or service.E-mail contact: melissah@lodinews.comLodi News-Sentinel is the sole judge of appropriate reuse and reserves the right to withdraw this permission at any time with written notice.Lodinews.com is a wholly owned division of the Lodi News-Sentinel. Note to Letter WritersWe encourage letters to the editor and appreciate those who submit them.One reminder: Letters should be the original creation of those who write and submit them.Especially in the digital age, it appears some writers are tempted to cut and paste the work of someone else into a letter to the editor. Please don’t.It is, of course, fair to quote a short passage and provide clear attribution to it.We want to feature the original thinking and views of local residents. Writers who submit the work of others as their own may no longer be welcome in this forum.
© Copyright 2020 Lodi News-Sentinel, 125 N. Church St. Lodi, CA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
